Bodha Talks: One chakalpatarupeshcho.
Bodha Talks: Hare Krishna, Hare Krishna. Hare Krishna, Hare Krishna. Krishna, Krishna, Hare Hare. Krishna, Krishna, Hare Hare. Hare Rama, Hare Rama. Hare Rama, Hare Rama. Hare Rama, Hare Hare.
Bodha Talks: So, Meta, we'll…
Bodha Talks: Very grateful to be amongst all of you.
Bodha Talks: Evening, finally, after many years of deliberation. Yeah.
Bodha Talks: There is an attempt to… stats on the input side.
Bodha Talks: And it all began with the one workshop done recently.
Bodha Talks: So I spoke on… The culture of Srinagar Bhagavatam.
Bodha Talks: introduction to Sudheya Goswami and Parikshit on the first day.
Bodha Talks: And I'm also delighted to… continue with the similar discussion on Parikshit Maharaj.
Bodha Talks: While we are discussing, Or we intend to discuss?
Bodha Talks: things from the Bahamas.
Bodha Talks: Is Grace going to the room?
Bodha Talks: has, spoken a lot of Mahabharata From… socio-political and… Target perspectives.
Bodha Talks: In an attempt to try to assist him, I should… share certain things from Malawi.
Bodha Talks: So today, I'll just introduce you to a very basic
Bodha Talks: scripture of Mahabharata, and also certain basic terms.
Bodha Talks: See… The Vedic literatures are composed in the language of Sanskrit.
Bodha Talks: Which is very rich in its expression.
Bodha Talks: And… When you're… and the whole literature is composed in poetries.
Bodha Talks: So when you want to write something in poetry, it must… not lose the Essence.
Bodha Talks: that it is so poetic, but the essence is lost. At the same time, it has to be also very concise.
Bodha Talks: Poetry means a few words concisely arranged.
Bodha Talks: In a manner that you can recollect, you can remember.
Bodha Talks: That's the meaning of poetry.
Bodha Talks: So, earlier days, because there were not many things to reproduce, and The technology for reproduction.
Bodha Talks: Or preservation was more on the leaves. So it was impractical.
Bodha Talks: that you cannot replicate. Today, you have photocopies, you know, you can copy, paste, direct messaging, it's a total digital photocopy, basically.
Bodha Talks: You can transfer, it was so easy. Earlier days, it was not like that.
Bodha Talks: So, when you have to remember a lot of things.
Bodha Talks: Then, you have to devise a method, and that method was poetry.
Bodha Talks: And therefore… When you read the ancient literature, even when it concerns with astronomy, Mathematics.
Bodha Talks: Physics. Everything is in form of poetries. Sutras and… compositions.
Bodha Talks: formulas are, like, Because there was no way of reproduction.
Bodha Talks: And in that way, a lot of…
Bodha Talks: Sciences were also preserved. Now, when you compose something in the poetic sense, in place.
Bodha Talks: That the person who is writing should know the language properly.
Bodha Talks: And the person who is memorizing or knowing also should know the language. Otherwise, you know the…
Bodha Talks: Mantras, and it makes no sense.
Bodha Talks: For example, these days, people do participate in Vagavedita competitions.
Bodha Talks: No.
Bodha Talks: Bhagavad Gita is a spiritual literature. The word competition can never…
Bodha Talks: Combined with it, how can you… as long as you're in the mood of competition, there is no question
Bodha Talks: Competition destroys spirituality. That's the basic premise that we want you to understand.
Bodha Talks: A competitive mind cannot hold spiritual.
Bodha Talks: deeper spiritual values.
Bodha Talks: You can be religious.
Bodha Talks: You can have competition on becoming very famous by doing charitable.
Bodha Talks: Or being known as a hierarchy, or… Maricela Tapasiakiya.
Bodha Talks: You can have competition everywhere, so that is not very spirited.
Bodha Talks: So, competition is not the basis of spiritual learning.
Bodha Talks: So anyways, what would be the combination lengths? If the people remember ZRA and their scopas.
Bodha Talks: For thousands of Sherpas, but… They don't know the meaning of it.
Bodha Talks: So in earlier times, knowing or memorizing something also implied that you also understand it well.
Bodha Talks: Then we need to also understand these aspects, because The modern minds get cheated.
Bodha Talks: By itself.
Bodha Talks: Just because we remember a few shokas, or we put it on our walls, or here and there, but we don't have that proper
Bodha Talks: a comprehensive understanding of those words. That is what is called as Bodhi, which is
Bodha Talks: The name of our program, trying to make an implicit sense.
Bodha Talks: Auruskar Bhawat.
Bodha Talks: So, Bhakyartha and Bharat in Hindi. You understand the difference?
Bodha Talks: So, can somebody give me an example of Vakyartha and Bhavartha? Give me an example in your own… Understanding.
Bodha Talks: Wow, what is the meaning behind this?
Bodha Talks: Yeah, so give me an example.
Bodha Talks: You may be using many things in your day-to-day life.
Bodha Talks: I don't know if I'll be able to answer this question.
Bodha Talks: But I can't say this.
Bodha Talks: I don't even exactly know.
Bodha Talks: Because then we'll go, like, hey, bye.
Bodha Talks: To praise yourself, like that. It gives you… Yeah, it means like that.
Bodha Talks: You will need it.
Bodha Talks: Can I put that as the last name? George Salinas That's right, I'm done.
Bodha Talks: Shana means what?
Bodha Talks: Shara, in Maharashtra, in the writing needs.
Bodha Talks: twice.
Bodha Talks: Life's first.
Bodha Talks: smart, that is called shine. So it's a very good term.
Bodha Talks: Okay, Shannon, I'
Bodha Talks: But when you use it in modern sense, how do you… what is the bhawat of it? Overstrong. Overstrong. Okay. I mean, dead shaman. So, dead means…
Bodha Talks: One and a half, more than the complete Shana. So, it's actually a glorification. You are dead Shana, means you are more than Shana. But if somebody tells you, actually, dead Shana, what do you feel?
Bodha Talks: Beginning, second. Yeah.
Bodha Talks: So, Dil Shah Nagar, how are the head?
Bodha Talks: You're idiot.
Bodha Talks: Don't act smart. You're very intelligent.
Bodha Talks: So, this is the difference between Vakyartha and Khawartha.
Bodha Talks: This is Hindi.
Bodha Talks: Cuba.
Bodha Talks: Actually, actually, actually, actually, actually, actually, actually, actually, actually, actually, actually, actually, actually.
Bodha Talks: Ki meine bohot samnya hai aapko, aur uske baad bhi, ultimately jap karne ki baadi hai, aapne wahi ky
Bodha Talks: Thank you.
Bodha Talks: Besides, I don't have money. I don't have money. I don't have money. I don't have money.
Bodha Talks: Ya, khet mein leki jawa, so si bais hai se leki, lekin paan
Bodha Talks: Teacher kari paani ho. Akshat sutra karke lekha ho, toh bhi paani dikha ki ho So, Gao make it…
Bodha Talks: Kheh, kheh, kheh, kheh, kheh, kheh, kheh, kheh, khe So, very, very spontaneous means
Bodha Talks: The… the… a typical buffalo is un… Tenable… If it sees water.
Bodha Talks: You cannot control your instincts.
Bodha Talks: Toh gayeb hai spani mein ka literal matlab hai, ki bais spani mein chali gaye. For sa bhawat hai k
Bodha Talks: Of course, I wasn't thinking that.
Bodha Talks: So, anyway, this is Vakyartha and Bhavartha. Many of us use, if you observe in your day-to-day life.
Bodha Talks: a large part of your most effective communication, whether it is in praise or criticism, is always in the Bhavarka.
Bodha Talks: Not in work yet.
Bodha Talks: Sentences, by themselves, have less meaning.
Bodha Talks: If the overall context is not understood.
Bodha Talks: And therefore… It is extremely… Important.
Bodha Talks: To have some sense of how these beautiful… how these beautiful words or sentences are composed and arranged.
Bodha Talks: And once you understand these things in our Vedic literature, it all becomes a very beautiful experience to start understanding things in a very different way.
Bodha Talks: So… The word Mahabharata.
Bodha Talks: Maha means great, and Bharat does not mean the…
Bodha Talks: Kalki Bharat, but it literally means… That, which is… spoken about…
Bodha Talks: about the descendants of Bharat Maharaj
Bodha Talks: So, we had discussed it the first day of, Bhagwat Sabha, if you remember. Vasudev, Vasudev…
Bodha Talks: Bhagwat, Bhagwat, Bismillah, and Bhar
Bodha Talks: So, when the descendants were stories about the descendants of Bharat Maharaj, and because those stories were really grand.
Bodha Talks: enrich and condense their understanding, therefore it is called, it was called as Mahabharata.
Bodha Talks: That's the basic premise of it.
Bodha Talks: In the Srimad Bhagavatam, we… one of the first prayers which we chant in the invocation itself is…
Bodha Talks: So this Mahabharata is glorified in this verse.
Bodha Talks: So, before the beginning of Bhagavata.
Bodha Talks: So, Srimad Bhagavan is essentially a literature Which…
Bodha Talks: Which is written with the presumption that you already have some understanding of Baha'i.
Bodha Talks: to relish. Bhagavatam, you have to have some understanding of Bhagavatam, otherwise you'll not be able to relish it properly.
Bodha Talks: So, in the composition of that, the prayers are done. Narayanam, I bow down to Narayan, Narayan Namaskirtan, to Narayan, Narayan Narayan.
Bodha Talks: Devi Saraswati.
Bodha Talks: We asked them.
Bodha Talks: From whom?
Bodha Talks: So, Jaya was the original name of the Mahabharata literature.
Bodha Talks: It was… it had 8,000 verses.
Bodha Talks: It is not that Mahabharata was only 8,000 verses, but it was… it's a compilation of the literature, so it was condensed in the form
Bodha Talks: of 8,000 versus… which later… Was expanded to 24,000 versus… called as Bharat.
Bodha Talks: The same name or the same what we read the description and then later we asked them compile it.
Bodha Talks: in,
Bodha Talks: In 150 verses, which glorified the… or which gave the summary of the chapters, the title of the chapters.
Bodha Talks: Have you all seen Gita? So, in the index book, with the chapter, there are a few lines which they explain.
Bodha Talks: It's not just the name. Like, Aranya Kaand Head, I think, was maybe your chapter said, Uzge?
Bodha Talks: Provost, could you start?
Bodha Talks: So, we are given 150 verses. We wrote the chapter summaries of
Bodha Talks: the Mahabharata, and then he expanded it into 600,000 verses.
Bodha Talks: 300,000, where… So, will you do the day with us?
Bodha Talks: We're rather written for the game task.
Bodha Talks: 150,000, where for the petrols, 100 and… 40,000, where for, the…
Bodha Talks: Gandharva, Yaksha, and all, and then 100,000 were for human beings.
Bodha Talks: So, this literature was written by Vyas.
Bodha Talks: But it was expressed by different people. So, Narad revealed the Mahabharata to the Devatas.
Bodha Talks: Rishi Deval, he revealed the Mahabharata, to the pictures.
Bodha Talks: Shugadeva Swami revealed the Mahabharata to the Yaksha and Akshas.
Bodha Talks: and asuras, and it was Vaishyam, Vaishyam Payan, or Vyas, who revealed the Mahabharata to the human.
Bodha Talks: So, what we need…
Bodha Talks: today is roughly 100,000 verses of 6 volumes of Databricks, if you know, that is the model which we have.
Bodha Talks: Okay?
Bodha Talks: That is basically a discussion what had happened.
Bodha Talks: See, this book was… the Mahabharata was composed after the Pandavas left.
Bodha Talks: this plan.
Bodha Talks: Someday, we may come to that discussion, that Swadhara and all. It is a very heart-touching moment and discussion.
Bodha Talks: And I think we did not go that place when we went to Bhagavan. We went to the gas station.
Bodha Talks: Yeah, but we need to go that side. That's where we are.
Bodha Talks: I think it was cloudy or something.
Bodha Talks: So that route is there, from where the Pandavas left this world.
Bodha Talks: So, we asked who is writing the Mahabharata. It is very important to know.
Bodha Talks: Vyas was not an outsider who is writing history, like, for example, when I write about Ellipsis Shivaji Maharaj.
Bodha Talks: Now, I'm an outsider, because I'm not part of… it's a history, 500 years ago. So you can get okay if you're doing things.
Bodha Talks: But we are smaller insider.
Bodha Talks: In what sense?
Bodha Talks: Because VRs have 3 sons.
Bodha Talks: The dashboard?
Bodha Talks: Pandu and Liduri.
Bodha Talks: It was… Mahabharata is basically a literature which is describing the conflict between Kauravas, who are the Sanat.
Bodha Talks: And Pandavas were the son of Pandu, all under one clan called as Kuruvaj.
Bodha Talks: 2… America, we asked, produced, Anybody knows?
Bodha Talks: Ambika, sorry, through Ambika, he produced the trash. Through Ambilica, Pandu.
Bodha Talks: And then, Vidur was through?
Bodha Talks: Through the Dacio?
Bodha Talks: I'm begun.
Bodha Talks: So when Dhritarashtra was born, he was born blind.
Bodha Talks: So then, Satyavati told her that, please go to Biyans again.
Bodha Talks: in a proper state of mind, so that you got a good sense. So instead of sending… instead of keep going, she sent her male male servant, Parishthama, that you go.
Bodha Talks: So she went, and then Madhur appeared. So that's all. So these three personalities are key personalities when you're reading Mahabharata.
Bodha Talks: Vidhul comes as the most wise, wisest, one of the wisest and helpless person.
Bodha Talks: Pretty fast, right?
Bodha Talks: He's one of the stupidest and most powerful person technically on the throne.
Bodha Talks: And Pandu, the most qualified, but physically unfit.
Bodha Talks: What a combination. So…
Bodha Talks: Somehow, when you read Vedic literature, or even if you look in your life, you will always find, like, these kind of combinations.
Bodha Talks: Humilitating.
Bodha Talks: Kahi kahi mara, das chahi hai se hogya red chah
Bodha Talks: By hand, I have a meeting with them.
Bodha Talks: Are you hurting at the moment?
Bodha Talks: Hi, someone may I help? Hi, Paribas.
Bodha Talks: So, in that sense, the Raman and Mahabharata is very light and empty. You take the characters.
Bodha Talks: Even in our own Ashiya, I used to tell.
Bodha Talks: I thought I saw my camera keyboard on, but it… So we're gonna be…
Bodha Talks: Bhagta looga apa se milte looga regik hai sa
Bodha Talks: Mandir mein pipeline sakurte kesar.
Bodha Talks: I am curious.
Bodha Talks: This week, and I think someone may have got plenty to make.
Bodha Talks: Rajiv Rajiv Rajiv Rajiv Rajiv Rajiv Rajiv Rajiv Rajiv Rajiv Ra
Bodha Talks: So, I said, how do I go good? No, thanks for that.
Bodha Talks: So, when he is there, he will be there. Ultimately, he will be there, he will be there, he will be there.
Bodha Talks: Margota.
Bodha Talks: So… Bhawat prayas kami ke baad bhawanne hi prednan hi, ki hari kpatra ko shaspare dekhi
Bodha Talks: Agar aapko le tegi aapke jiwen me aapki sita
Bodha Talks: So, after this one, after this one, after this one, after this one, after this one.
Bodha Talks: Okay, wait, couldn't be I'll keep delivering my plan.
Bodha Talks: Aap hi ki le koi dhrit rahas toh hoga, aap ke jeevan mein bhishna bhi hoga, guru drone mein hoga ki, aal
Bodha Talks: Okay.
Bodha Talks: Maybe they can be tangled.
Bodha Talks: They will react, they will get confident.
Bodha Talks: And therefore, in the beginning itself.
Bodha Talks: When the scriptures were… was written, okay.
Bodha Talks: So even I'll come to this point, just remember, remind me. Where I was continuing?
Bodha Talks: Because, so these three… Vyas Devi is not an outsider, he's an insider who is writing this after… it is his own children and own progeny, he's seeing that way, and then after their departure, he's writing as what has happened, and also reflections.
Bodha Talks: So… Is Klantika bara mai?
Bodha Talks: Pooja Janmejaye. Janmejaye is the son of…
Bodha Talks: But it should. But it should. Is this enough?
Bodha Talks: Okay.
Bodha Talks: Arirang News. Arirang News.
Bodha Talks: But if she was cursed.
Bodha Talks: To die in 7 days because he did something which was so unnatural for him.
Bodha Talks: Wouldn't give us somehow, may wouldn't give Gulmehi me Where's the caveat here?
Bodha Talks: Kuwaiti?
Bodha Talks: As a Khatriya, you need to engage in some warfare and keep those skills of killing and sharpness, you know, so hunting wild animals was a natural thing.
Bodha Talks: So that your stiffness, dexterity, attention, and all those are always very well maintained.
Bodha Talks: Because animals are very good in those things than human beings. So in terms… in times of war.
Bodha Talks: That works. So, Karishit had gone for a hunting expedition, and then he feels thirsty.
Bodha Talks: Which is a very natural thing.
Bodha Talks: But in this occasion, he thinks that, let us go to any nearby jungle, Himachal Pradesh, or Hoga Pradesh.
Bodha Talks: The phone jacking, or behind the sheet.
Bodha Talks: Shanika, what's the procedure?
Bodha Talks: Unone manga pani.
Bodha Talks: I don't know if you have any Dl Question I have here.
Bodha Talks: It is… it was very unnatural for Parikshit to exhibit a sense of anger or disappointment at that time.
Bodha Talks: But… When you read Mahabharata.
Bodha Talks: See, Ryazdeer has written Mahabharata in such a manner that every view, every character is described with this humanness.
Bodha Talks: The writing of Shiva Bhagavatam is such that every character is described with their divinity.
Bodha Talks: There is a difference.
Bodha Talks: So…
Bodha Talks: When you read Mahabharata, you will have a different experience of those personalities, but at the same time, hari get ki kitna bhi dhush kho ya kitna mi hamsa mein kami hai tohi ko tayo ki. Antha karan mein ham ko lata hai
Bodha Talks: Me bhagwan ke ashrai ka, it pattra baan sakta hai.
Bodha Talks: I deserve to be given compassion and kindness. So that kind of tenderness is there in every… even the most rude people. So Bhagavatam deals with that aspect of an individual.
Bodha Talks: Mahabharata is dealing with the brutality.
Bodha Talks: Jiwen Charate Samay.
Bodha Talks: Jeev pariksha wo se hamsa ko vujarna patta hai. Most of the times, we know when we are committing a mistake.
Bodha Talks: And most of the time, we are also helpless, we are clueless, and we have no other option.
Bodha Talks: Jeevan ka design e SI?
Bodha Talks: Vajpande mi bhoda chalak bhai jajeevan. Vajpande to muj
Bodha Talks: So I think, go go here. I think I want.
Bodha Talks: No, I can't wait.
Bodha Talks: How many of these people have died? How many of these people have died? How many of these people have died?
Bodha Talks: Ki dharungka palam karni gaya baat
Bodha Talks: it is not easy for us also to keep a religious code of life. It is always an extreme struggle.
Bodha Talks: What to top off all of?
Bodha Talks: the other members of the society part of the Dhrayastha Ashram, then you have to deal with something called as my children, my family.
Bodha Talks: But it becomes… Exponentially complicated, but tough wish I know.
Bodha Talks: So… Yes, sabaj naa ki koi bhi lepti
Bodha Talks: Jeevan chalte chalte ghul nahi kareg You're gonna pay.
Bodha Talks: Aur other aapko koi jeevan mein SRF ki nila hai, ki jo
Bodha Talks: The summer demo will be on Monday.
Bodha Talks: Ahi nila apko vetti ek sannyasi mein hin hindi kega. Ek babaji mein hin hindi kega. Sansar mein shari bharen kiya to dosh yukta hai.
Bodha Talks: Doshi matra kamyada ho sakti.
Bodha Talks: Mutta iska ho sakta ki maine bhavna se kuch galat nahi kya aa gaya actions se bot melty ho. Because if me aa bhi, for a discussion procedure, living alone koi gole ki mein, she has been flawless
Bodha Talks: And that is not to be… we should not be surprised by that.
Bodha Talks: Because those things have been discussed off.
Bodha Talks: Well, I'm discussing in the context of correction.
Bodha Talks: Flawless work.
Bodha Talks: Blessed by Krishna.
Bodha Talks: Grandfather Arjun.
Bodha Talks: Father died in the heart of the battlefield in saving them.
Bodha Talks: Raised by Yudhishthir.
Bodha Talks: raised by the Pandavas.
Bodha Talks: To dara ji, to give my prayers hai, whatever is
Bodha Talks: Ek matra kuru waan jyo sambar ai wala tapu wohi tha. Dhonu saith ke family. Sekhi bhi kaoro bhi jya mal gaya etu hungko bhi esala gaya
Bodha Talks: Move as expected.
Bodha Talks: He was not a guy who was a person who was raised with difficulties, and Bachchanya told me, "Sangarsh mein baat tutu mein mein karke pala bada toh esses sanskar teh ki beg boros feel karna pada hai kabhi instinct laha hai".
Bodha Talks: He's raised with a similar school, Jayat Kamunti.
Bodha Talks: So, instinctively, also, for him to do something like that, to insert the sage, he finally did it, and he said.
Bodha Talks: Ushika HKMSX… Sukhasa.
Bodha Talks: Some might be, but I know it's it's all time to take
Bodha Talks: It's a black and Canadian, yeah.
Bodha Talks: Could you lecture me?
Bodha Talks: So, maybe make habit.
Bodha Talks: Ki kuch logo tees karna, aur ajwi het
Bodha Talks: So, Gabby, Gabby In our college days, people would be very nervous.
Bodha Talks: It was a very nervous situation. It was a very nervous situation.
Bodha Talks: What have we already added to ATTS?
Bodha Talks: Instinctively, I happened to tease some of them, and spar some moments.
Bodha Talks: So, somebody snapped at me.
Bodha Talks: Are you able to get a copy of the deck?
Bodha Talks: Casey, I'll turn your initial hand over there.
Bodha Talks: I'm Mumbai.
Bodha Talks: Emma.
Bodha Talks: Why? Because I had that Sanskar, which just instinctively came. What I'm trying to say, Parishit did not have any of that, and he instinctively became arrogant.
Bodha Talks: So, it's not instinctively arrogant, rather.
Bodha Talks: Therefore, the scriptures also, and he also sees this, that this cannot happen without a divine intervention.
Bodha Talks: So, this is not a small incident, first of all. Many people think that array keys are very arrogant, isn't it?
Bodha Talks: To learn about the Canada for Bikes, Nathan already takes you seriously.
Bodha Talks: But, Parikshit Nadar was not like that.
Bodha Talks: As soon as that happened, he got cursed.
Bodha Talks: To dial in 7 days.
Bodha Talks: This is the premise.
Bodha Talks: He could have denied the curse, Now, correction, Mara, it's
Bodha Talks: The interesting part of his name.
Bodha Talks: Also, which is, can you give me the power command for this person?
Bodha Talks: The part… why he was named Parikshit is also very important to understand.
Bodha Talks: So, anyways… Parikshit Maharaj is The paid snake touchup comes.
Bodha Talks: And he… it kills Burj Khalifa.
Bodha Talks: Later… Janmejer, who is his son?
Bodha Talks: When he comes of age, he feels that my dutiful and righteous father was wrongly killed.
Bodha Talks: by snakes. So he decided to do a yakya, which is called a Saripasapa yakya, where all the snakes of this universe would be destroyed. He wanted to destroy species, the entire species, powerfully to decode.
Bodha Talks: Okay, that's it.
Bodha Talks: Sankalpa na karma, ki mein puri ek yoni puhi naasth karma. Toh wo bhau nahi toh hona chahiye. Ayak selka hamari paas chyoti chhatiye. Namari shaktiye an
Bodha Talks: takeover is not natural.
Bodha Talks: Hannah?
Bodha Talks: Perfect. So it sounds superficial, but… Imagine.
Bodha Talks: Someone… Time to… destroyer species.
Bodha Talks: Vyas Dev Keshat.
Bodha Talks: No, no, it's okay. I just need to refer to one of the locals.
Bodha Talks: Putra, should they will show me?
Bodha Talks: then… Vaishalpayana, who was also his disciple, and some other disciples, they had come.
Bodha Talks: So, Vyasadeva had taught this Mahabharata scripture to all of them.
Bodha Talks: Means he had spoken about these stories. When Jammajer asked to Vyasa that I want to know the entire history of my family.
Bodha Talks: key… Kaura aur pandav ekhi parivaar ke loo, itni bhishal yudhne?
Bodha Talks: And it's like a symbol
Bodha Talks: Por usi youth mein, bangwe dita golige.
Bodha Talks: So, he said that I want to know in detail.
Bodha Talks: And that time, Vyasadev instructed Vaishyan Payana that you please speak.
Bodha Talks: And what version plan? Why version plan? Spoke to Jeremy, Jeremy.
Bodha Talks: is what is called as Mahabharata for mortal human beings.
Bodha Talks: I'm just giving up.
Bodha Talks: So this Mahabharata, the original Mahabharata, see the original Gita?
Bodha Talks: is the battlefield of Krupshita. Mahabharata was the battlefield of destruction of snakes.
Bodha Talks: So, the discussion is going on, right? So, the discussion is going on, right? So, the discussion is going on.
Bodha Talks: So the duration plan starts really fine.
Bodha Talks: And he speaks the Bhagavatam. Later in that whole assembly, along with Sudhey, Vaswami, and others,
Bodha Talks: Aram, Aram, sorry, Sunday Goswami was there. Then, later, Sunday Goswami…
Bodha Talks: Is that Sukhatal, with Tarikshit Maharaj and speaking things?
Bodha Talks: And then, one of the persons who was there in that discussion was Suta Goswami, if you…
Bodha Talks: I have read the Bhagavatham.
Bodha Talks: Or, his name is Ugra Shrava Sutra.
Bodha Talks: Ugras Ravi, the actual name, Suta, is kind of the s
Bodha Talks: They say Vyasa is technically kind of a surname, like a designation, you can say. So, when somebody says Vyasa, which Vyasa, then you say Dvaita Vyasa, Krishna Dvaita Vyasa.
Bodha Talks: Like that. So, many vyasas will be there. So, many suttas will be there. So, which sutta? Ugrasya Sutta, who spoke, or he's also known as Sauti, who spoke the Shimadhana. So, when Sutta goes from Iran to Naivisharanya, the sages ask him.
Bodha Talks: That you were there for this beautiful discussion, Between Shubdev and Parikshit.
Bodha Talks: So, please tell us everything in great detail.
Bodha Talks: So they were the ones who, Insisted to know about?
Bodha Talks: Put a mahalo at
Bodha Talks: And Suta Goswami also then, again, spoke this to the CJs of Nimisharanya, along with the Raghavatam.
Bodha Talks: So… Technically, this literature is coming from very enriched people, very enriched mouths.
Bodha Talks: Asked by very beautiful, tapestry kind of people, and so on.
Bodha Talks: So… In the Shiva Bhavatam, in the first canto itself.
Bodha Talks: the meaning of the word Parikshit, or why Parikshit was called Parikshit, is described.
Bodha Talks: So, the first kind of chapter will… Text number 30.
Bodha Talks: That word says… Sir Asia loke loke wi kya para parikshit iti yat prabhuhu.
Bodha Talks: Purva Drishta Anu Dhyan Pariksheta Nareshka Eva
Bodha Talks: So, his son would become famous in this world as Parikshit, because he would come to examine all human beings in his search after that personality whom he saw before his birth.
Bodha Talks: Thus, he would come to constantly contemplate him.
Bodha Talks: So, Parishit Bharaj, Parishit Ka Arata Sanskrit Pasha
Bodha Talks: Iksha is the root word, basically.
Bodha Talks: But it is the suffix, sorry, prefix.
Bodha Talks: And TA is the prefix, so… Iksha comes with 2C.
Bodha Talks: To examine, I don't know what kind of prediction, but now Nirikshankarna.
Bodha Talks: they're, up there's no… a big shadow.
Bodha Talks: Apekshak is over there. Expectation. Expectation. Apekshan means to see or to understand. And apa means towards. So, apekshan means towards and understanding.
Bodha Talks: So, I'm coming towards an understanding. So, that is how that works. Apa means going to…
Bodha Talks: Pari means going inside, means examining. They can now observe karma, investigate karmas for pari, for example.
Bodha Talks: Upek Shawerpe.
Bodha Talks: The root word again, iksha, upeksha.
Bodha Talks: I've got that. I appreciate this.
Bodha Talks: insert, ignore, Let's go ahead and take a look at your calendar 05.14.25
Bodha Talks: So, that is infection. So, I understand ICSHA means to see imperfection, and
Bodha Talks: The fixed means one who has been examined.
Bodha Talks: Mala jiski pa riksha ho chu ki hai, jiska pa riksha ho chu ka hai, ya jo halti hika pa riksha
Bodha Talks: So, Usturup said, but it should work at the end.
Bodha Talks: Jiske cheripreka padikshan ho chukaan, aur ho ho werkti nahi hai, jo ek anum ho ki padikshan kar waha hai baar ba
Bodha Talks: Wo kya hai ho kaan? Jaap wo gar On?
Bodha Talks: Ashwatthama ne, jadramasthra chodha. Toh Bhagwan Krishna swear ne, Anggu te ke root mein pratak bhai, mein garbh mein chhota se wo embryo stage mein ka hai. Sini bhai, he was like
Bodha Talks: He was in an embryo stage, just formed.
Bodha Talks: with the basic thing, and he took… he had the diversion of Krishna. That experience was very deep.
Bodha Talks: And with all subsequent experiences of life, he was trying to examine with reference to that.
Bodha Talks: Okay, there you go.
Bodha Talks: Group se ham sab hai na, ham sab mein panikshit maharaj hai ka Only with a long case.
Bodha Talks: Did you have comparison curtain, huh? Most of the time.
Bodha Talks: Comparison, an internal aspect.
Bodha Talks: External aspect me.
Bodha Talks: JSEC object in comparison to Koini Ghanta.
Bodha Talks: Manlo is government.
Bodha Talks: behind the cheeses of that one.
Bodha Talks: So, whoa, you see their friends, man.
Bodha Talks: But everyone can see that, thanks, man.
Bodha Talks: Talk to Larry, I can't mount this account
Bodha Talks: So, Harry, the comparison is an internal function. Externally, you can take orange here or apple here.
Bodha Talks: Toh agar aapko orange pasante, toh aapko aapko muni muni jaye fruit pasante, toh
Bodha Talks: But Cusco externally compared to Cisco Railway.
Bodha Talks: Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
Bodha Talks: So, nobody does objective comparisons.
Bodha Talks: The meaning or the bhavartha of the comparison is basically when it is an internalized thing.
Bodha Talks: under JCD Mano.
Bodha Talks: Aapne ki si bhi nahi ice cream khaya, krupya karge dhan bhurva bhi is chich ko savanji, yeh wal
Bodha Talks: You mind if I make… oh yeah, I still can't
Bodha Talks: Bhojan ka swad wo AC se denyota.
Bodha Talks: Roti bhariya bharati. Sajji bhariya thi dal bharati thi chawal. Aant me aapko jo anubha ho bharati hai ho ke bharati hai ho chawal or roti ka nahi ho tai. Agar wada lag se khao gaya to shaivatna anand nahi hai, agar gima jo kuch me jo yog ho ta
Bodha Talks: Rasa is not in that object, it's in the combination of too many things.
Bodha Talks: In the aesthetics, in the time, in the manner in which it is served, and so… and then you get a… what is finally?
Bodha Talks: Under Experience.
Bodha Talks: Oh!
Bodha Talks: Waheed chiri jo bahad hi swadhi shay man lo, usko aapne das din lara tark maya.
Bodha Talks: To aapko wo anum hog lengi aata But I would.
Bodha Talks: Kya acha khana hai? Bho, acha khana nahi taga hai? Acha khana nahi taga hai? But essentially, aap andar husi anubhav kurdhum rekhi ho jab aapne sa kaya
Bodha Talks: So, comparison is an internal function. It has nothing to do with external objects. External objects are just a medium. If the most attractive object is repeated to you, it vanishes.
Bodha Talks: So here you can hear her echoing.
Bodha Talks: Constantly.
Bodha Talks: Personally, in Ghana Suna, we say, peace version, pachas version. Hafta sona auske baad, mujhe dusra Ghana jiye jo mujhe bilkul
Bodha Talks: Puri Jeevanmay.
Bodha Talks: I see a new hope for the whole planet,
Bodha Talks: Kijo Hong Kong?
Bodha Talks: How you been, honey?
Bodha Talks: So… Mein Mahabanjati, huh? Tomojek, Anubhav Miltani, kinus anubhavan mein
Bodha Talks: Filmmaker, he's helping Sankoj hota hai, say, ghutan siya hoti, ya tul azad hona ha
Bodha Talks: Waheed ekti pachis sahte hai rura tavagwan ke sabne mujhe baabal na Hang on.
Bodha Talks: Vesa hum mein bhai bhanta hum, mein beta bhanta hum, mein pati bhanunga, mein putra bhanunga. Aar ek Anubhav mein koshish karlah hum. Kuch samyete vadho Anubhav.
Bodha Talks: And there's it.
Bodha Talks: Luke told you about that.
Bodha Talks: Lekin, uskajo… Puski jo kalpanathi, the original, the first experience of that feeling, I'm chasing that.
Bodha Talks: Exactly same thing happened with parachuting, a different thing.
Bodha Talks: For most of us, we don't know what we are chasing, Q.
Bodha Talks: Ha, okay, I bring a patiya, patiya bandhi Guru Bhangevi Degiya, Shishu would you…
Bodha Talks: Okay, we're gonna carry yesterday.
Bodha Talks: I'm… I'm dated. Sunny, I see you, and then…
Bodha Talks: Well, there are people, so I want to retire from, from my, from my duties.
Bodha Talks: But that's also retired.
Bodha Talks: So get out of here. So get out of here.
Bodha Talks: Apne aapko sthai karne telhe vu ibhar ke liye, ibhar ke liye, pariwar banata hai, aur padme ussi cheek se mukta hoode
Bodha Talks: You guys don't cut in.
Bodha Talks: Yeah, Kevin, can I ask you something?
Bodha Talks: From which have you come in?
Bodha Talks: Can I just put it in? You can't go on it.
Bodha Talks: Y escogar tije, y escogprogram tije, y escogmande tije, y escogare tije, y escogzone tije, y escarcas, gall
Bodha Talks: bus.
Bodha Talks: It's in my new group.
Bodha Talks: Oh, me too, guys. You know, that silk one, you know, that silk one.
Bodha Talks: But, it's sunsetting.
Bodha Talks: So… Anyways, I lost the point.
Bodha Talks: Thank you.
Bodha Talks: So, most of us…
Bodha Talks: Hamko agar bhadwan ka sakshaat anubhav nahi hai, toh bhi anundar se hami aisi anubhav ko dhut rahe hai
Bodha Talks: Abhita, journey khatami din yudho kho lalsa. Was tuki thi, there was tuki… Hamlo, actually, was tuki ki chesna geki ham, was tuki
Bodha Talks: Actually, it was 2K. Binagar, one of our videos.
Bodha Talks: So, hame, agar koi SHC is nahi hakne lagi, khirmi sansar ke wastu ome ham chipat nahi kaare kuri thara se. Uljiye mue hai, ek hota ki ulje ulje rena, aur ek hota ki an
Bodha Talks: Announced, how are you?
Bodha Talks: Mallah bhuti mai chhodni septa, andar se tad, tada bhara hai, jal raa hai, chhodni se
Bodha Talks: Yeah, I love it.
Bodha Talks: Yeah, how's it going?
Bodha Talks: Jeff?
Bodha Talks: Agar aapko bhagawanka tora kinchit matra bhi anubha hogya, to aaki dashankya ho.
Bodha Talks: If you're so restless, Even after all your acquisitions and whatever you have.
Bodha Talks: And in the sense of comparing them, I'm better than others, you know, whatever.
Bodha Talks: Still, you're not settled emotionally or internally.
Bodha Talks: What would be your condition if you truly experience something highly spiritual.
Bodha Talks: how suffocating and difficult it will become to live your current life. Because your current life is incapable
Bodha Talks: to hold you… Can you see?
Bodha Talks: I'm saying… with all our acquisitions, which is nothing but a creation of our own mind.
Bodha Talks: Islami AIC is Sundarai. Sundar is the word for Sanjeev. Mujhe Sund
Bodha Talks: Yeh painting kya toh, mujhe sundar lata hai, ya sahi chee chee hai, mere man ka
Bodha Talks: I'm not pointing out in person. Huh?
Bodha Talks: Hamara ji hamara ji bhar hai, hui hamara ahamkar tai k
Bodha Talks: How many girls? How many girls? How many girls? How many children?
Bodha Talks: Hamara hi creation, jo hamare ego ko saru karte huye banaya gaya hai, ussi me hamara dan gh
Bodha Talks: But I'm…
Bodha Talks: Jyo humne logo se lado jagad ke ki yehi beste hoon aaya, ussi me hamara dam ghut raha yeh hai sansar ka swarukh, basically. Jaat isme dam ghut raha hai, aur ham yaha se ma
Bodha Talks: To kya hoda usne artika jisne chalang lagana usko lagana yaha ki dari chalang ni laga sakta akiu wudar pakar laga yahawan ki.
Bodha Talks: To feel, to feel, to feel, to feel, to feel.
Bodha Talks: Means, he will be celebrating not, not celebrating, but he'll be like.
Bodha Talks: You may say kahiti mani lehre.
Bodha Talks: So then you will suffocate, that's what I'm saying.
Bodha Talks: Anyone with a spiritual experience, material life will become difficult.
Bodha Talks: Difficult does not mean that you will become incompetent.
Bodha Talks: Aqua, you can bus make cover, Java lands.
Bodha Talks: When will I see? Madhu bhiya mawka, mileya bhiya chhoru. Bahana dhundu ve. Jaise bhiya bhi
Bodha Talks: Waisa, Ulta, Ulayaga, ki mat ka, niklu yaase aur isthara se ki, ka bis d
Bodha Talks: So, parekshit, wo getti hai, jisme bhagwan ko anhu haru kar liya, aur kus anhu haru ke baad jume ice cream hai khana hai. Wo anhu haru, ite na acha, wo baad baad next
Bodha Talks: Yeah, I'm ready, I'm ready, I'm ready.
Bodha Talks: Jai kirtan bareya talagi nustirola kuchand
Bodha Talks: To wo jo anubhav krishna ka hogya parekshit ko. Wo anubhav ko. He was not examining malaya asami ki har lekti ko. Akho se kya hiya bhai pareksh
Bodha Talks: Voyeni negre dekhiya krishna hai ke liye krishna hai. Asami. Vo hari sambant ko puri dhar mi group se. Vogi unka putra va matl
Bodha Talks: Extended Pariva Raja The or Rajya Tha, Sapkus De Mantri De through every experience.
Bodha Talks: Very devotionally and in a dharmic manner, he involved himself trying to extract that same experience which he got in the womb.
Bodha Talks: So, in every experience, he was investigating…
Bodha Talks: But money can do that. Please make.
Bodha Talks: Every relation. Like, when we go into any relation, hamara prior experience si transcendence ka hai, nahi toha maa aisi yule jaato. Aur ugar say se, tochar thinki baal thadka purgam.
Bodha Talks: Okay, he wants it. He wants it.
Bodha Talks: Basically.
Bodha Talks: See, but it's a marriage, it's a person.
Bodha Talks: For us, we celebrate life.
Bodha Talks: Why? Because we see meaning only in being alive.
Bodha Talks: Volkan sostai ist anubhanke liye.
Bodha Talks: Mujhe ki aki a bada nodi. Aap isko prehinke isme deko aatika lese, lerke lerki ne preh
Bodha Talks: Toh doon doko ko mil lek lek.
Bodha Talks: Ma'akobibada so much thing.
Bodha Talks: Vitality Group, what else am I saying?
Bodha Talks: Ki kuch nahi, hamagar sharif se dhi mein se te to atma ke roop mein. Hamme lege hai, dek mister kodi bajao. Ksaat na atma kya ka mein? Yahweh atma koi, yahweh koi. H
Bodha Talks: Apne milan ke liye, sansari baada vanjata hai, apne milan mala premise millek liye, sherebni baada vanj
Bodha Talks: Agar shahdi ri kroop mein bhi yeh se bhoota hai, toh jis ko aad bhi hai kni kano bhoor bhoor bhoor bhi kin
Bodha Talks: Kyuki ho dekte gais aatma se bhi ji kya hai bhi ke ja. Pehle bhi gya bharat satta hai, I don't know
Bodha Talks: Okay, but how do we do it?
Bodha Talks: Senses are incapable to help you emotionally.
Bodha Talks: It is just not… they are not designed for that.
Bodha Talks: Buy ourselves water liquor.
Bodha Talks: Bahar ka aaja, he is, like, dumping kaloto jo, aadhar pin faktifi ro kuta bhi jo, dumping hiji ki nahi indri ho, mekhya kalo is indri haka. Ek bhi alu bhao jo, yeh indri hai d
Bodha Talks: Je mera man, jo aneg aatat piyo shalil ke dwara jo upa diya bantihih usme uj Okay.
Bodha Talks: Should you get one open? Yeah, look, ma, Bob, hi, Ben.
Bodha Talks: Abjam chhote bachche thi, chhoda baby, bwaan na tai tap kya.
Bodha Talks: Ki bahut chote na nahi shishu ko toh hum, mala beta bheti bheti
Bodha Talks: Bala ki bolte, right? Bala… shishu, is it?
Bodha Talks: Gender meaning was therefore a very different.
Bodha Talks: You know when I say infant girl and infant boy, it's an infant.
Bodha Talks: Zero padi, basically. Eki padi, eki padi, shali, b
Bodha Talks: Diri diri olad ka, laddi ki yawa nahi sab karte. Toh vaisya shik Upadhi matlab.
Bodha Talks: How are some of you out there?
Bodha Talks: Mankawa.
Bodha Talks: usme jab dosh ho to usko kayte kubagi. Madlan meren mangka bhava se May, Indiana.
Bodha Talks: So, I'm going to actually have help here.
Bodha Talks: Nima Tesharire.
Bodha Talks: Tumare bhav mein doche. Adhelp mein darshtikun se aap jubi kuch aap bhutto dein usmein bh
Bodha Talks: Servo, padhi, vinir muktam. Servo, padhi, vinir muktam. Padhi, vinir muktam.
Bodha Talks: Upadhi matlab jobhav hamko apne sorupse galaturupse wastuk karta hai.
Bodha Talks: Mary, Baptistia, Mary, Paribas, Cantua, Sepala. Por mujiaco, Pastor, and Jandiri, Lumosi, Parib
Bodha Talks: Avdiya Tarasana, Bhulik liya to me Bhagwan
Bodha Talks: You can count it there, Daniel.
Bodha Talks: like… Eleguete necesica. Vaguanque derche en hotel turan
Bodha Talks: Okay.
Bodha Talks: If you have a sudden death, actually, most of us, we want the darshan in our house. We don't want darshan that way. That means we are not ready for
Bodha Talks: darshan, essentially. It's a beautiful cheating or packaging which we are doing on our devotional activities.
Bodha Talks: So… and basically, human beings is full of contradictions, if I go…
Bodha Talks: That part of the contradiction bothered.
Bodha Talks: So… Have a good show for that.
Bodha Talks: Adosho anupada. Ja doshne rehta usko anupada kete, isme bhi ko doshne
Bodha Talks: But if she's married, she won't know who Raja
Bodha Talks: Na kisi ka putra ya kultra hai, abhuge avekiska kya hun jubihenne bi mea apne aapko ni pai chan para
Bodha Talks: Salsa leito ulher aja na nunca d
Bodha Talks: Pare khanda na family ka anubhav diriy
Bodha Talks: Lekin Anders se mein aap portion nahi hora hai jo oche ek tarshan
Bodha Talks: Uttarapre. To JC Uncle Sharp, Milan.
Bodha Talks: I say we calculate.
Bodha Talks: And there's the old person nowadays.
Bodha Talks: I didn't walk, I'm nearly a bike.
Bodha Talks: By a million.
Bodha Talks: So, I'll be transparent with you.
Bodha Talks: If you want to go, you can go ahead.
Bodha Talks: Can we… it is 6.06, how long we should continue? 5.10.
Bodha Talks: So he was young, so that was not a justified, thing that he gives up his body.
Bodha Talks: Don't make a hockey on people's
Bodha Talks: I will not use mystical powers, so that is excuse to give. I will not use mystical powers, so that is excuse to give. I will not use mystical powers. I will not use mystical powers. I will not use mystical powers.
Bodha Talks: So, externally, he put all efforts that he should not die, internally desiring intensely that he should die.
Bodha Talks: There is prediction.
Bodha Talks: So it is not that his love for death.
Bodha Talks: It was… his… intense desire to experience God beyond the limitations of the mind, body, and intelligence.
Bodha Talks: Something like that.
Bodha Talks: to experience God, Beyond the limitations of the senses, which is the body.
Bodha Talks: the limitations of mind, which is through the Upadhyaya, and the limitations.
Bodha Talks: of the intelligence.
Bodha Talks: Exactly.
Bodha Talks: Actually, Hamza EATs Secondly, my sister would say, I'm so lucky you got there, without a grand experience.
Bodha Talks: So, when a person seeks shelter of Krishna, yeah, I say, jab yahdi is, is cheek ka kar samadh mein aay, yahdi ki jeeban mein har jo panisthiti hai, wo mujhe…
Bodha Talks: Wo ek bhawan ka ashre living a kaaran bhansat kaar
Bodha Talks: Jeff will use some of it, I got it.
Bodha Talks: Dab pi bhire dhire bhagwaan ako uss sahnach ke proof p
Bodha Talks: Take Adan Padani on virtual route.
Bodha Talks: Then you accept that every situation of life… Every situation is an opportunity to surrender to Krishna.
Bodha Talks: It's a very nice this year.
Bodha Talks: Every situation is an opportunity to surrender.
Bodha Talks: So… And we all are also exactly…
Bodha Talks: It's in the same line, it's just that…
Bodha Talks: Except for the remembrance of Krishna.
Bodha Talks: Yeah, then.
Bodha Talks: So when you read Mahabharata and Bhagavatam, this is the premise It's.
Bodha Talks: Have the question also to you.
Bodha Talks: For them, life and death Are all the same.
Bodha Talks: Shereen Milewala Vekti Joe Apniakosh Shaheen Samarasthan, he feels that his I like… In a very wrong way.
Bodha Talks: JP, you're always aligned, right?
Bodha Talks: You're essentially never dead.
Bodha Talks: So you can say, Bhagwan ki Kupa said, Bhoda iski samal yane lag jaye
Bodha Talks: So here, jiya mein aanandi aan baai. Kyuki har mruttiu ya har baai, jiya koi mruttiu
Bodha Talks: and we cut them away.
Bodha Talks: Sri Chhodi Chhodi Mushriya, jiska aan dhyat mi, e ras chhakne lekta hai, muska h
Bodha Talks: To then you are.
Bodha Talks: all pure…
Bodha Talks: No more work.
Bodha Talks: So, stop here.
Bodha Talks: Any questions or comments?
Bodha Talks: At the end, at the end of my life.
Bodha Talks: We still feel attached, although… Tripadni per yabi, kumi chizok yabi, or tripad shab
Bodha Talks: Auld ruppe esanya fasterete, ne? Essek kami geden te durja, durja, durja lekar, sakshme dur, nonya lekjato lekta pakit pakit bakar. W
Bodha Talks: Jese padi shikko, pakarna aka hai wo hapnil l
Bodha Talks: kari maine kaana jo, kaana jo, maine kucha also renden kaya uska, memory uska, experience itna, internal itna, strong ro, ki iske baat nahiya so gula jaan, rasgulla, yaise, ila dia, ananda raha ha
Bodha Talks: So, where's your experience here, Mohammad?
Bodha Talks: Wani. And help me jeevan mein west side. Kimchi kmatra kuch to west side experience hunna awe sha ke. Nito pirwa adharma pura ritual kai ruple le tai. Mala kabhu darshan karo se lah. Mala kabhu darshan karo se lah. Mala
Bodha Talks: Gangodi.
Bodha Talks: Oh, we're not in Gastoria now.
Bodha Talks: Huh?
Bodha Talks: Ritual to speech is ritual, yeah.
Bodha Talks: Yep.
Bodha Talks: So, internally, our work is based on Krishna. It is based on Krishna. It is based on Krishna. It is based on Krishna.
Bodha Talks: Living group, travel now, eagerness and belonging.
Bodha Talks: Jose, may I ever… Agrabuja, akashi, nayi berengenando, mayto k
Bodha Talks: Give me a minute. If you're okay.
Bodha Talks: Majla ko, aapki ka, aapki ko kurpa kaani padegi na, mere, mere Indreva, Sharira, Raja, limited mind and intelligence.
Bodha Talks: Sadena garnea quixe purez el lutenei o pate. Por eliri lutenei o pate.
Bodha Talks: Harjeet Mein Sangarshay.
Bodha Talks: A UK electrical.
Bodha Talks: Aap aase pupad rita manda si manda yaisa karak rita si motamati karak si. Is condition na mai aapse k
Bodha Talks: The question of… Kuch tu do? Akhozene kaire gumenko?
Bodha Talks: Good.
Bodha Talks: I'll go, yeah, to Hong K
Bodha Talks: So you pay $8 in that day?
Bodha Talks: Yeah, so, it was kind of…
Bodha Talks: For devotees to get attached to their deities also, they need some experience.
Bodha Talks: Like…
Bodha Talks: One time, I know a devotee, just like all of us, like, not like a very tapasri kind of a year to do. But they were doing Aarti.
Bodha Talks: So, one Friday, their younger daughter… maybe the other one can help me, there's a flower there.
Bodha Talks: This mother was actually doing Aarti, and then she saw that Radhanani is actually, like, doing the flower.
Bodha Talks: Tu mako laga aki meinen meinen brahm hai, wo mako e b
Bodha Talks: She's just, like, ordinary commoner, like, all of us, doing duties.
Bodha Talks: So, she felt like she's just conquering things in the mind. So, I asked her, I said, what is this? She said, what is this? She said, what is this? She said, what is this? She said, I don't know. She said, I don't know. She said, I don't know.
Bodha Talks: Then she realized that this was an…
Bodha Talks: Actual PIN, we can have it.
Bodha Talks: Now, for most of us, See, the DT is same, like gravitation.
Bodha Talks: But we, we, we, we, we, we, we, we, we, we, we, we, we, we, we, we, we, we, we, we, we, we, we, we, we
Bodha Talks: Hadar Logic, Hadar Lecture.
Bodha Talks: At one flower moment.
Bodha Talks: Like that.
Bodha Talks: Krishna, I have so many such stories of contemporary people having many such…
Bodha Talks: it explains it, but maybe someday I'll speak that. These people, they get attached to the deities and to the whole process of Krishna Mukti.
Bodha Talks: Only on that.
Bodha Talks: Unkofi Bhargavatam, samajh mein aaya tak, vitak ho, chaitanya chaitany
Bodha Talks: I'm going to tell you. I'm going to tell you. I'm going to tell you. I'm going to tell you. I'm going to tell you. I'm going to tell you. I'm going to tell you. I'm going to tell you. I'm going to tell you.
Bodha Talks: No, it's okay. It's okay. It's okay. It's okay. It's okay. It's okay.
Bodha Talks: Jenna, vajir y Sandra el lueye. Y esque vina me caruja. Parul tuvo y son
Bodha Talks: So, wo open wala leko kehl kehlan medega
Bodha Talks: Oh, you see, it worked, and he got hung ahead, but we're happy with this call.
Bodha Talks: Okay.
Bodha Talks: Kahimi.
Bodha Talks: Something you will get an experience to pull yourself in for a month, six months.
Bodha Talks: So, for me, it was then.
Bodha Talks: Can you send me a card? Can you send me a card?
Bodha Talks: They're gonna upload, you guys, what are you guys doing?
Bodha Talks: then you will start seeing DPs differently. You will start seeing directions differently, you will start seeing parallelograms, because maybe…
Bodha Talks: You don't want to do anything at the reach. Although, externally, it has a… So…
Bodha Talks: or… and the aspect of experiencing God can never be…
Bodha Talks: Through scriptures, or a design of a discipline.
Bodha Talks: That is a facility.
Bodha Talks: So that we become mature and ripe to focus on important things, and then you attract those energies.
Bodha Talks: But apnea, that thing will force the transcendence to come, that is not possible.
Bodha Talks: Y pukare.
Bodha Talks: Two finger roller, basically.
Bodha Talks: Oh, thank you.
Bodha Talks: Sherry.
Bodha Talks: Like, you know, Monday through Friday.
Bodha Talks: Guru Cherandi Pacha is not embed Technically, it's the worst.
Bodha Talks: So, you see, I'm here for 10 minutes. I'm here for 10 minutes.
Bodha Talks: Or Rona, you know. Let me cry in this emptiness.
Bodha Talks: If you give me the strength, if you cannot fill this void, I'm not going to fill with the whole garbage, just for the sake of it.
Bodha Talks: I would rather cry and suffer. It is okay. Now, that strength will come only when you lose something.
Bodha Talks: Otherwise, that vacuum of emptiness, we will fill it with garbage. We'll fill it with cheating experiences, again, despite having 10 experiences now.
Bodha Talks: I hope.
Bodha Talks: Thank you.
Bodha Talks: Unbelievable.
Bodha Talks: I'm on the page and look at it.